♪♪♪
Ora yudeki, ora yudeki
Ora-yudeki, Ora-yudeki
Tat-tat-tat-tat.
Now move your feet, move your feet, move your feet, move your feet, move your feet, move your feet, move your feet, move your feet, move your feet
Move your foot, move your outer foot, move your foot, move your foot, move your foot, move your foot, move your foot, move your foot, move your foot, move your foot, move your foot Move your feet, move your feet, move your feet, move your feet, move your feet, move your feet, move your feet, move your feet, move your feet, move your feet, move your feet, move your feet, move your feet, move your feet, move your feet, move your feet, move your feet, move your feet, move your feet, move your feet, move your feet, move your feet, move your feet, move your feet, move your feet, move your feet, move your feet, move your feet And..,
Thank you for your time.
Thank you for watching!
I got everything ready yesterday. I think I'll do VR today.
Good morning and we're ready to go.
I'll always have to be you, so I'm happy to have you as an added bonus
Good morning, it's alright Hold me lovingly
Even now, I'll go on and on with you
Then do it in a woman's voice
Do you think this country is a dance?
Don't look at the members, look at the audience and say you think this is the country.
I think it's better if you don't see the audience, because you can see their reaction when you change it.
If you change it, everyone will do the same thing.
If you don't change it, you can see what's behind you, but not what's in front of you.
If I can't go home, I can turn around and go home.
Yeah.
Lee Lance W.
Kankai Shapeyathers
I don't like it.
I knew it.
Even in your dreams.
There's only one
It's the only one
Not now, not yet
About love About love About love
Come on. Open.
Congratulations.
That's right. As a team.
So you're ready?
We're ready.
Let's start the music!
Wait a minute.
This is for experience.
Come on.
Ooh-oh-oh-oh.
Ah.
This world, look at the smiles on their faces.
The first fan meeting con series is over.
It's over.
2nd con coming soon?
The first one might be done at this time around.
Certainly.
But, you know, we used a lot of space this time.
I think you're going to do it.
I'm also very particular about the music.
I've made up my mind.
I'm going to share it with you.
I kind of saw it.
First time?
Many of you are seeing it for the first time.
Well, let me introduce Kira and Sweatshirt.
Please introduce the sweatshirts.
This is how the GIRLS' CARDS family ting sweatshirts look like this time.
Then, please go to the good place with pom-poms two by two.
Muzu.
Muzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz.
Next, what's your favorite part for Joie?
The fact that it can be worn by both men and women.
That's a good point.
The colors.
Everyone should try it on with the color in mind.
Everyone should change their clothes.
I hope you and your fans can look forward to the various ways to wear the costumes.
Let's go for it!
5,6,7,8
1,2,3,4
Five, six, seven, eight.
Claire and Misaki are going to overlap a little bit, so
I'm sure the girls outside will be fine.
I'm going to swing once.
Five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four.
I didn't realize how far away you were.
I've always loved you, but I couldn't tell you
I can't tell you how much I've loved you.
This feeling that seems to be overflowing is supposed to be perfect
but I can't grasp it.
I'm going out.
Thank you for watching.
I hid the rainbow on Sunday.
I think I'll do a mise en scène today.
Good morning, are you ready?
Have a good day!
Have a good day.
Let's go
Good morning.
Good morning
Someday it will comeOne day it will come.
Till that day comes
Someday soon
Always near me, always soon
Inside of you
Today is the second performance, and at the end of the first performance, Yukarin-san told us about your feelings.
I think that your feelings are so high that you want to convey them to everyone, so don't stop, but keep your heads calm and believe in what you have done, and you will be all right.
Let's have a talk with the people of Osaka. Let's thank those who have done so much for us, and let's prove that we will continue to be okay on our own.
Yes.
Se-no, thank you very much!
Yes, sir.
Two times.
Good morning.
See you later.
Too late.
This way.
Thank you very much.
Good luck.
Bye.
Bye. - Bye.
See you later.
See you someday.
See you, Minami.
Let's go.
Sorry.
I'll go then.
Excuse me.
I went to the bathroom.
There's smoke.
It's emo.
It's not dust.
It's smoke.
Seino
Album Channel
The opening festival is about to begin!
We'll begin in two minutes.
Two minutes.
Shiritori!
Seino.
Apple, gorilla, lout, sanshoo.
Mimin.
Done.
I'll do my best.
I want sweets.
Instant runner.
Hah!
Kabrivos.
Chiksai.
Kablibos.
Yay!
Me
Jacket Jacket Jacket everyone Jacket on
♪ Everybody's wandering on ♪
♪ Who's got a Jacket on me ♪
Jacket Jacket Jacket everyone Jacket on
♪ My originality makes me wonder how sad I'll be ♪
Jacket Jacket Jacket Everybody Jacket on
♪ We are the new era
♪ So let's go hard
♪ Let's lift our hands to the truth ♪